Hello everyone and welcome back to this just in.
My name is Marco and I'm here with Bill.
Hello everybody.
And Scarlett.
Hello.
What's wrong, Scarlett?
Scarlett, are you okay?
You always introduce him first.
It's not fair.
I do?
Yeah, you do.
It's alphabetical.
Bill comes before Scarlett.
Yeah, that's true.
We're trying to teach a language here.
We've got to stick to rules.
Okay, okay.
Grammar rules.
Well, that's not so much a grammar rule.
All right.
So yeah, you guys may have noticed that I was absent for a couple of days.
I didn't notice.
No.
No, I did.
Well, maybe our community did.
It was quieter, definitely.
So I was away.
I went very, very far away, like 16,000 kilometers away from here.
My goodness.
I don't know how far that is, but it sounds far.
Sounds a long way.
It's really far.
I think I actually, the distance that I've traveled in order to go to Ecuador and then
come back here, you know, like round trip, I think that's enough to go around the earth.
Really?
I think so.
What was your return trip like?
It was the same way I came.
Oh, so you went to LA first and then.
And then to Ecuador.
Yeah.
Okay.
So was it LA Shanghai direct?
Yeah.
Oh, that's not bad.
But still it's like 12 hours on an airplane.
It's way more than 12 hours on an airplane.
Well, no, no.
Just that leg.
It's just that leg.
What's LA to Ecuador?
It's got to be.
It's another like eight or nine hours.
My goodness.
Yeah.
But you had a, you had some downtime in between.
You didn't just jump on another plane.
Yeah.
I jumped off a plane.
As well.
Yeah.
I went skydiving.
So, um, just went skydiving.
Yeah.
You know, just the daily routine, what you do, that's the type of person I am.
So anyways, uh, we have some great things set up for you guys this week.
On Monday we're going to be talking about daylight savings time.
Woo.
Yeah.
One of my favorite subjects.
I know.
It's actually, I would get really confused with this.
Why?
Why are we doing this now?
It's already, it just happened like a month ago.
Well, two months ago.
It did.
It happened in holidays.
November.
We have to wait till we go back.
Are you sure?
No, not only, we're not only talking about daylight savings time, but we're talking about
time zones.
Ah.
Okay.
Well, that's something that happens all the time.
Like, uh, yeah, like crazy time zones, like a country as huge as China only has one
time zone.
That is pretty crazy.
What is with that?
I don't know.
Beijing time all the time.
No.
Um, but yeah.
And apart from that, you know, the meridian, what's that one?
Oh, are you referring to the Eastern and Western hemisphere?
All right.
Was that proven?
The prime meridian.
Yeah.
I proved it.
We proved it.
Conclusively.
And it's the Greenwich line there.
So there is a Western and Eastern hemisphere.
Yes.
Apparently there is.
Of course.
Why wouldn't there be?
Do we want to get into this?
Bill was right.
All right.
So we're going to be talking about that on Tuesday.
We're going to talk about the movie, the pianist on our show.
Directors cut the pianist.
So who's this directed by?
I don't know.
What is his first name?
Walt.
Stephen.
Roland Polonsky.
No, no, no.
The Polish guy.
What's his name?
That sounds pretty Polish to me.
Yeah.
Well, I think it was a great movie.
I think it won a couple of awards.
Yeah.
It's supposed to.
It's really sad.
I actually, I almost cried.
I almost cried.
Does that not happen very often in cinema?
No, it does not.
It's not.
Except in Finding Nemo.
I cried in that.
When he gets separated?
Yeah.
Well, what about you?
No, no, no.
I can't remember which part I cried with Nemo.
Oh, it's happy after that.
Yeah.
Where's the sad part?
He comes back.
I think when his mom gets killed, it's kind of like a Bambi flashback.
Did you cry during E.T.?
No.
I bowled.
Really?
Just the entire time.
Scarlett, did you cry in Titanic?
No, I didn't.
I didn't.
I was very sad when Jack just went down, disappeared in the ocean.
But apart from that, no.
This movie is actually, it is sad, but it was really good.
And the way that he plays the piano, and it's actually based on a true story.
So that makes it even more interesting.
I always like movies that are based on true stories.
Wasn't Glory's Bastards.
Glory's Bastards was not based on a true story.
Any aspect of it at all?
At all.
None.
You cannot refer to that film as historically.
Oh man, that movie is great.
We've already talked about that.
Yeah.
I missed that one.
That was good.
All right, on Wednesday we have Natural Disasters.
Yes.
What is it?
Fun topic.
Yeah, it's such a fun week.
It's like sad movies.
Taxes.
All right, Natural Disasters are going to talk about like tornadoes, hurricanes, earthquakes.
Floods.
And what's happening recently with...
Insect invasion.
No, no, no.
We're having like a really cold month like all around the world.
Lizards.
Yeah.
Like in London, is it like snowing?
Yeah, snow is chaotic.
It's crazy.
And they don't know how to deal with it either.
Yeah, apparently they're not used to it.
And they're like, what do we do?
They're not used to like one bit of snow.
Should we drive or should we stay?
That's quite a nice English accent you've got there.
I try, thank you.
Scarlet.
Who's better?
I think mine is better.
Scarlet.
You're both really good.
Oh, very...
Do English people laugh at like American actors pulling off a British accent?
Yes, because they either do it really like London Cockney or really posh.
Oh, really?
Really, really posh.
Let's hear it.
What is that?
What does that even mean?
I can't tell the difference.
Give us an example of London Cockney and really posh.
A posh.
Do posh spice for us.
Posh spice isn't posh.
Her accent isn't posh.
Like a posh person is just really sort of very rah, rah, rah, rah.
Oh, darling.
Oh, that's absolutely fabulous.
That sounds like Winona Ryder, like Dracula.
Hello, darling.
Darling.
So very fabulous of you to meet me here.
That sounds more Australian.
I can't.
It's the same thing, man.
Outrageous.
All right.
So that's what's going on on Wednesday.
And on Friday, we are building our dream home.
Well, that is nice.
That is something jolly and happy.
It is.
Jolly good time.
And actually, you were a couple in that dialogue.
You guys acted out as a couple.
Yeah.
That's right, sweetie.
Oh, yeah.
Biscuit.
Why you wanted the skanky old-fashioned 60s house?
Actually, I was thinking about that yesterday after I got off work.
And I was like, actually, I kind of am into the older.
You would go into like a 60s style home?
I think if you combine those two, because in that dialogue, it was well, because you
could have like cool vintage lava lamps, furniture, but in like a nice open modern kind of floor
plan.
I don't think that would work.
I don't think that would work either.
You guys have no style whatsoever.
Would you have like the avocado green carpet?
No.
See, that's going way too far.
Like it's just the design.
The design of certain like couches, like couches from the 50s, like look cool and they look
cool in like modern spaces too.
I don't know.
I still watch the vinyl.
You guys.
He's getting angry.
He's like, what are you guys doing?
You guys are ignorant.
You don't know anything about design.
What do you know about design, Bill?
Oh, I know.
Oh, he knows.
Just don't ask.
You need to ask.
All right.
So those are our dialogues.
Our lessons coming up this week.
And that's about it.
Do you guys have any news?
Any announcements?
I'm going on vacation soon.
It was Bill's birthday yesterday.
It was my birthday.
It's really old now.
Happy birthday, Bill.
Thank you.
Thank you for lunch.
Both of you.
You're welcome.
You were feeling a little bit like getting over there, right?
A little bit.
I'm 28.
And that's, I mean, 27.
It's all downhill from now.
It's closer to the end of the day.
I'm 28.
And that's, I mean, 27 is closer to 25 and 25 is closer to 20.
Do you see my reasoning here?
Not really.
But now that I'm 28, I'm closer to 30 than 25.
You're already losing your mind.
Yes.
In school, they teach you to round up.
If it's like 25, you round up to 30.
That's pretty harsh though.
And 28 is definitely a round up to 30.
Yeah, for sure.
I mean, I round up.
27 was kind of a round up too.
I round up to 40 then.
It's a right there, but you're not in your 30s yet.
It makes no sense.
I round up to 40.
Yeah, no.
If we're doing zero to 40, I round up to 40.
So can we say I'm closer to 40?
That means we're all closer to 40.
Yeah, exactly.
Your math skills are terrible.
All right.
I have an open concept.
You're 28.
That's good.
28 is a good age, I reckon.
Really?
I think so too.
It's been absolutely fabulous.
All right.
Way to go, Bill.
Happy birthday, and Scarlett.
Yeah, Scarlett, what kind of news do you have?
She got her haircut recently.
Yeah, it's looking dashing.
Both me and Marco noticed.
Yeah, I noticed.
My family didn't even notice.
Really?
Wow.
Oh, Tarsi.
Your friend.
Yeah, my friend.
And a girl.
Your only friend.
See, and they say that.
And they say that.
Not my only friend, by the way.
Aren't observant, or that guys, we don't notice.
Yeah, they do.
See, we do.
Yeah.
Well, you too, do you?
All right.
That's all the time we have for today.
We hope to see you guys next time.
And be sure to listen to next week's lessons.
And if you have any doubts or problems, you can always reach us at support at Praxislanguage.com.
All right.
We'll see you guys there.
Bye.
Goodbye.
EnglishPod.com.